Guide to the Records of the North American Jewish Students Appeal, undated, 1962, 1964-1996 (bulk 1971-1995) *I-338 and *I-338A
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series IV: Beneficiary Grants, undated, 1971-1995; Boxes 52-61 (Folders 1-24).
  - Subseries 2: Grants Made by Program Year, 1971-1995; Boxes 52 (Folders 8-24) - 61 (Folder 1-24).
    - Program Year, 1989-1990
      - University of Michigan Prospect Advertising Grant, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - University of Minnesota A Shayna Maidel Theatre Production Grant, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - University of Minnesota Israel Action Committee Yom Ha'atzmaut Programming Grant, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - University of Pennsylvania Insight Outreach Chai Week Programming Grant, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - University of Pennsylvania Yugntruf Yiddish Leyenkraz National Conference Travel Subsidies Grant, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - University of Wisconsin Genesis Publishing Grant, [1989] (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - University of Wisconsin-Madison Progressive Zionist Caucus (PZC) Erel Margalit Honorarium Grant, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Campus Organization for Israel (COFI) Middle East Peace Process Seminar, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Wesleyan Hamakkor Publishing Grant, [1990] (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Yale University Chai Week Questions of Judaism Programming Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Program Year, 1990-1991
      - Baltimore Campuses Jewish Students Association Israel Week Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Beloit College Haggadah Replacement Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Brown University Mahberet Publishing Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Columbia University Perspectives Publishing Grant, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Denied Proposals, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Do the Write Thing National Symposium on Jewish Issues for Campus Media (General Assembly, 1991) Conference Fee Grant (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Georgia Israel Network of University Students (GIPAC)Building Jewish Identity Workshop Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Hamagshimim Florida Zionist Students Conference Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Macalester College (MN) Hebrew House/Israel Action Committee Israel Day Programming Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - McGill University Progressive Zionist Caucus (PZC)Compromising for Peace: Dilemmas Surrounding the Palestinian-Israeli Conflict Seminar Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Monterey Institute of International Studies Middle Easter Exchange Club The Israel Experience Film, undated, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Progressive Zionist Caucus (PZC) Shuli Eshel Film and College Tour Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Project Chai, Various Campuses Planning and Programming Grants, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - Recipients List, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 28)
      - Rider College and Trenton State College Programming, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - San Francisco State University Blacks and Jews Staged Reading Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      - San Francisco State University Israeli Science and Technology Fair Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - State University of New York-Buffalo Jewish Student Union 5th Annual Semi-Formal Funding Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 32)
      - Syracuse University Blue and White Campaign to Support Israel Emergency Funding Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 33)
      - University of British Columbia-Vancouver Israel Awareness Week Programming Grant, January 25, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 34)
      - University of California-Berkeley Ha'Doresh Publishing, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 35)
      - University of California-Berkeley Kol Ha Student Publishing Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 36)
      - University of California-Santa Cruz Progressive Students Union Speakers Honorarium Grant, Jan. 29, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 37)
      - University of California-Santa Cruz Progressive Zionist Caucus (PZC) Conference Student Subsidies Grant, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 38)
      - University of Illinois-Urbana Champagne D'Varim Publishing Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 39)
      - University of Maryland-College Park Yom Ha'Shoah Vigil, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - University of Michigan Jewish Peace Fellowship Speaker Honorarium Grant, undated, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - University of Oregon Israel Week Programming Grant, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - University of San Diego TAGAR Zionist Student Activist Movement Conference Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - University of South Carolina Southeast Regional Conference Spring Retreat Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - University of Texas Russian Olim Housing Studio Project Funding Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - University of Wisconsin-Madison TAGAR Zionist Student Activist Movement Why Israel? and Israel Independence Day Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Campus Organization for Israel (COFI) Yom Ha'atzmaut Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Washington, DC Campuses Israel Task Force John Rothmann Honorarium Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Washington University-St.Louis Hillel Sarah's Song Theatre Production Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Wesleyan University Hamakkor Publishing Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Program Year, 1991-1992
      - Brandeis University Hirhurum Publishing Grant, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Brown University/Rhode Island School of Design Broadway Bound Production Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - California State University-Long Beach From Ashes to Rebirth Programming Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - California State University-Northridge Round Robin Volleyball Tournament Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Columbia University Lights in Action Start-up Funding, undated, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Columbia University Perspectives Publishing Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Cornell University Am Echad Shabbaton and Kristallnacht Programming Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Denied Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Denver-Area Campuses Freedom Week for Ethiopian Jewry Grant Proposal, undated, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Genesis and the Big Bang, Dr. Gerald Schroeder Lecture Tour Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Jewish Student Services of Metrowest (NJ) Yom Ha'Shoah Campus Tree Planting Program Grant, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - McGill and Concordia Universities (CA)Kavana Publishing Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Ohio State University Hillel Winter Midwest Conference Programming Grant, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Ohio State University The Guardian-Ha-Shomer Publishing Grant, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - Polytechnic Institute of New York Jewish Student Union Russian Jewish Programming Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Princeton University A New World Order? Elie Wiesel Lecture Student Reception Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - Reconstructionist Rabbinical College (PA) Talmedi Chaverim Publishing Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Recipients List and Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 29)
      - San Francisco State University Progressive Jewish Student Union Panel Presentation Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - Simon Fraser University Israel Week Honorarium Grant, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - State University of New York-Albany The Spirit-Ha Ruach Publishing Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - University of California-Davis Jewish Culture Week Programming Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - University of California-Santa Cruz Women's Tour for Peace Funding Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - University of Delaware Hebrew Bayit Programming Grant, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - University of Florida Jewish Student Union Council Jewish Radio Hour Broadcasting Grant, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - University of Illinois D'Varim Publishing Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 37)
      - University of Illinois Pro-Israel Education Council Israel in a Nutshell Seminar Grant, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - University of Maryland Jewish Leadership Training Seminar Grant, undated, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - University of Maryland Promoting Peace in the Middle East Region (PRIMER) Resource Guide Publishing Grant, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - University of Michigan Celebration of Jewish Arts David Grossman and Debbie Friedman Concerts Funding Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - University of Rochester Yom Ha'Shoah Programming Grant, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - University of Texas Jewish Film Festival Funding Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - University of Virginia Hillel Professor James E. Young Lecture and Seminar Funding Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee TAGAR Chapter Israel Programs Fair and Masada Press Publishing Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - William Patterson College (NJ) Jewish Students Association Community Model Seder Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Yale University Friends of Israel Deadly Current Film and Discussion Programming Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - York University Israel Youth Concert Funding Grant, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Program Year, 1992-1993
      - Alliance for Judaism and Social Justice New York City Regional Conference Funding Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), Philadelphia Area Conference Transportation Grant, [1993] (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Brandeis University Hirhurum Publishing Grant and the Giving-Doing-Caring (C-D-C) Network Funding Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Brooklyn Law School Weekly Study Discussing Group Programming Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Brown University Kol Ishah Women's Group Women's Shabbaton Funding Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Columbia University Avodnah Dance Company Breezes from Andalusia: Dance, Spain, and the Jews Production Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Denied Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Duke University Israel Public Affairs Committee Solomon Perel Lecture and Europa, Europa Film Honorarium, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Elon College (NC) Holocaust Seminar and Letters from Leodakia Performance Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Sukkah Project Building Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - McGill University Undergraduate Journal of Jewish Studies Publishing Grant, 1993, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Memphis State University Israeli Independence Day Celebration and Fair Funding Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Middlebury College and Williams College Weekend at Williams Conference on Jewish Identity Funding Grant, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Muehlenberg College (PA) Passover Seder Funding Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Polytechnic Institute of New York Jewish Student Russian Jewry Programming Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Progressive Zionist Caucus (PZC)Visions for Peace: An Arab-Jewish Dialogue Campus Tour Funding Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Recipients List and Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Stanford University and Ryerson Polytechnic Deadly Currents Screening and Simcha Jacobovici Lecture Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - State University of New York-Albany The Spirit-Ha'Ruach Publishing Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - State University of New York-Binghamton Jewish Cooking: Our Tradition Programming Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - State University of New York-Stony Brook Shelanu Publishing Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 32)
      - Texas A & M Fish Camp Orientation for Jewish Students Funding Grant, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - University of Arizona Kol Koreh-The JournaI Publishing Start-Up Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 34)
      - University of California-Davis Jewish Cultural Week Programming Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 35)
      - University of California-Long Beach Israel Awareness Week John Rothmann Lecture Honorarium Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 36)
      - University of California-Los Angeles Israel Action Committee "Piece of Peace Israel/Egypt Peace Agreement Commemoration" Funding Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 37)
      - RESTRICTED MATERIALS University of Illinois D'Varim Publishing Grant RESTRICTED MATERIALS, 1992-1993 (Box 33 (59), Folder 11 (38))
      - University of Massachusetts Zamir Radio Show Broadcasting Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 39)
      - University of Michigan Annual Conference on the Holocaust Solomon Perel Honorarium Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 40)
      - University of Michigan Israel Michigan Affairs Committee (IMAC) Transportation Grant, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 41)
      - University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill The Jewish Tarheel Publishing Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 42)
      - University of Orgeon Yavneh Publishing Grant, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - University of Texas-Austin Film Festival and Kosher Meals on Campus Grants, 1982, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - University of Virginia Jewish Life at Mr. Jefferson's University: An Historical Exhibit Grant, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - University of Wisconsin-Madison Jonathon Kessler Middle East Lecture and Invisible Thread Photography Exhibit Funding Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Yale University Shabbaton Retreat Funding Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Yale University Urim v'Tumim Publishing Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Program Year, 1993-1994
      - Baltimore Inter-Campus Yom Ha'atzmaut Extravaganza Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Boston University Israeli Independence Day Celebration Funding Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Bowdoin College If Not Now, When?: Jewish Ethics in the 21st Century Second Annual Conference of Jewish Students Funding Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Brooklyn College A.B. Yeshoshua's Possessions Hebrew-Language Theatre Production Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Bryn Mawr/Haverford Holocaust Memorial Week Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - California State-Long Beach Lag B'omer Film Festival and Concert Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Denied Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Emory University Israel Activities Week Programming, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Georgia Tech University/Atlanta Young Jewish Adult Agency (YAD) Holocaust Remembrance Week Programming, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Hillel Council of Greater Boston A New Generation of Jewish Women: Weaving Our Tapestry Conference Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Inter-Campus Council, Baltimore Area, Chocolate Seder Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Center for Learning and Leadership (CLAL) Shabbaton Funding Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - McGill University Undergraduate Jewish Studies Journal Publishing Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Northwestern University Yom HaShoah Name Reading Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Recipients List, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - Southern Illinois University Aviva Kemperer The Life and Times of Hank Greenberg Lecture and Film Clip Viewing Program Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - Stanford University Shared Creativity: Visions of Community Inter-City Outreach Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - State University of New York-Albany Rabbi Avi Weiss Holocaust Commemoration Lecture Program Grant, undated, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - State University of New York-Binghamton Middle East Cafes Inter-Community Dialogue Programming Grant, undated, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - University of California-Davis Koleinu Publishing Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - University of California-Santa Barbara Holocaust Remembrance Week Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - University of Miami TAGAR Mid-Year Zionist Conference Funding Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 29)
      - University of Michigan Holocaust Remembrance, Dr. Leon Bass Lecture Program, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - University of Michigan Israel Michigan Public Affairs Committee (IMPAC) AIPAC Conference Attendance Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - University of Michigan Progressive Zionist Caucus (PZC) Yossi Melman Meet the Press Lecture Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - University of Minnesota U.S. Holocaust Museum Travel Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 33)
      - University of Oregon Yavneh Publishing Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - University of Texas-Austin Jewish Film Festival Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - University of Toronto Images Publishing Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - University of Western Ontario Solomon Perel/Europa, Europa Lecture and Screening Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - University of Wisconsin Israel Independence Weekend Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - Vassar College Ba'asham-Noisemaker Publishing Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 39)
      - Washington University (St. Louis) Elie Wiesel's Trial of Go d Production Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - Wesleyan Havurah Prayerbook Publication Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 41)
      - Wheaton College Making Our Own Space: A Women's Shabbaton Programming Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 42)
      - Yale University Faith and Art: A Festival of Religious Expression Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 43)
      - Yale University Magevet Spring Concert Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 44)
      - Yale University Model Israel Knesset Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Program Year, 1994-1995
      - Atlanta Jewish Young Adult Agency (YAD) Chaim Potok Lecture,Who Am I? Shabbaton and Claudia Stevens Performance Grants, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Binghamton University A Jewish Woman's Dialogue: Commonalities and Differences Forum Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Bradley University Holocaust Memorial Day with Dr. Leon Bass Lecture Funding Grant and Poster, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Columbia University First Annual Yiddishkeit Festival A Shtetl Wedding Performance Grant, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Columbia University Perspectives Tikkun Olam Issue Publishing Grant, undated, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Columbia University Raphael Society Jewish Medical Ethics Forum Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Cornell University Passover Freedom Seder Intercultural Programming Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Denied Proposals, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Long Island University Jewish Russian Heritage Club Hebrew Lessons Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Princeton University Multicultural Seder Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Recipients List, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Stanford University Members of the Tribe: A Weekend for Jewish Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual College Student and Young Adults Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - State University of New York-Albany Reform University at Albany Chavurah (RUACH!) Programming Grant, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - State University of New York-Albany RZA/BETAR/TAGAR Michael Eglash/Aliyah Lecture Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Tufts University Conference on Ethnicity and Feminism Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - University of California-Berkeley and Mills College Miriam's Daughters Publishing Grant, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - University of California-Berkeley The Jewish Renaissance: Revitalizing Our Community Seminar Grant, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - University of Michigan Annual Conference on the Holocaust and Hillel's First Alternative Spring Break, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - University of Oregon Eco-Ruach Retreat Funding Grant, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - University of South Florida Israeli Dance Workshop Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - University of Texas-Austin Jewish Film Festival Funding, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - University of Wisconsin Israel Independence Day Celebration and Art Spiegelman Lecture Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Washington University (St. Louis) Bio-Medical Ethics Shabbaton Programming Grant, undated, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Yale University Model Israeli Knesset Funding Grant, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Series V: Federations, undated, 1971-1995; Boxes 61 (Folders 25-30) - Box 94.
  Arranged in five subseries:Subseries 1: Council of Jewish Federations (CJF),Suberies 2: General Assembly (GA),Subseries 3: Large City Budgeting Conference (LCBC),Subseries 4: United Jewish Appeal (UJA), and Subseries 5: U.S. Cities and Canada.
  Series V contains material reflecting the relationship between the APPEAL and the Federations at national and local levels. This includes the formulation of budgeting strategies and presentations, CJF memos and correspondence, Trustee quarterly board meetings, APPEAL-CJF committee planning, General Assembly conference materials, and correspondence between the APPEAL and local, donating Federations. Materials include documents on the budget certification process, audit guidelines, budget digests, task force and committee documentation, financial reviews of the NAJSA, and LCBC minutes and memos. The Series is divided into five Subseries as follows.
  - Subseries 1: Council of Jewish Federations (CJF), undated, 1971-1995; Box 61 (Folders 25-30) - 64 (Folders 1-3).
    The Subseries is arranged in alphabetical.
    Subseries 1 documents contact on the national level with the CJF, including general updates, announcements and regulations from the CJF, plus correspondence between the CJF and the APPEAL. Box 61, Folders 27-30 contain correspondence that traces the development of the NAJSA and its relationship with WUJS and NETWORK, though the relationship between the two latter organizations is discussed in more detail. General files and correspondence in Box 62, Folders 3-9 also contain correspondence, but the overall nature (particularly in regards to the years of 1989-1994) of the files focuses less on correspondence than printed documentation from the CJF.
    Other documents include Budget Digest drafts and correspondence regarding those drafts. NAJSA was represented on several committees sponsored by the CJF including the College Youth and Faculty Programs Committee, Leadership Development Committee, Task Force on Services to Jewish University Students and the Women's Committee on Russian Women. Of particular note is the documentation on the Women's Committee on Russian Women, in which Susan Dessel served as Chair from 1978-1979. Ms. Dessel and several committee members traveled to the Soviet Union, meeting with refuseniks as well as attending protests in Moscow. Her observations on the condition of Soviet Jewish women is included, as well as a confidential memo to Glenn Richter of SSSJ concerning a planned protest in Moscow on June 1, 1978. Press releases from SSSJ concerning the actions of Soviet Jewish women refuseniks are included. Box 63, Folders 2-12, holds documentation regarding the APPEAL's participation in CJF quarterly Board meetings regarding planning for the above-mentioned committees and task forces as well Trustee meetings from 1987 and 1989.